

PROFILE SUMMARY

I am a Deaf woman who used to communicate using sign language during interviews that required a personal interpreter. I completed my Diploma in Information Technology (Software Development) at Belgium Campus iTversity for three years, plus one year of self-development at Botlhale Village, which subsidized the Belgium Campus iTversity for In-Service Training, and one year of the IOCO Software Developer Graduate program.

I am a flexible and friendly person who works well in a team as well as on my own because I like to set goals for myself that I will achieve. I also have good listening and fast learn. I have a creative mind and am always eager to take on new challenges.

WORK EXPERIENCE

June 2022–Current | The Digital Academy, Johannesburg, Gauteng **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER LEARNERSHIP**

- Work in team and self-manage also willingness to learn new languages programming.
- Build collaborating on a website development team.
- Design and build websites using simple HTML and CSS
- Techniques for logical problem solving and error detection

March 2021–September 2021 | Za Wit (Skills Programme), Centurion, GP **CLOUD COMPUTING**

- Understanding of how to work with virtualization Azure cloud computing service and Google cloud computing service.
- understanding the implementation of multi-factor authentication (MFA) for all cloud administrator accounts to increase security.
- understanding cloud computing, network architecture, APIs, web services, and other concepts within a cloud environment

C

(071) 986 4573 [SMS ONLY]



siyandakopolo@gmail.com



https://github.com/SKopoloza895

EDUCATION

June 2022 -Current| SpecCon Holdings (Pty) Ltd IT System Support NQF L5

Feb 2016 -May 2021 | Belgium Campus ITversity **Diploma In Information**

Diploma In Information Technology

Feb 2010 -Nov 2010 | NID College Certificate Of Office Administration

Jan 2007 -Dec 2009 | St Thomas School for The Deaf

Matric

- English (FAL)
- Life Orientation
- Mathematics Literacy
- Business Studies
- Hospitality Studies

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Graphic Design

February 2020-January 2021 | IOCO Subsidy EOH, Pretoria North, GP

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER GRADUATE

- Perform self-development and advancement.
- Researched and developed new technology designs.
- Work as a team on developing an interactive and dynamic website

February 2019–September 2020 | Botlhale Village Subsidy Belgium Campus, Centurion, GP

IN-SERVICE TRAINING

- Html5 and CSS3 supported project managers in determine milestones and project scope
- Created interactive websites with software development department using backend and frontend framework
- Lifecycle (SDLC) created spreadsheets using Microsoft Excel for daily, weekly and monthly reporting contributing as team leader and member learning from working with experienced software developers.

June 2012-September 2013 | Checker Hyper, Edenvale, GP

RETAILER OPERATIONS LEARNERSHIP

- Process Payments and purchases on the POS system
- Maintaining and controlling stock losses
- Receive on the floor back
- Data Capturer in the receive